<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<item><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 14:08:20 +0100</pubDate><title><![CDATA[Pellet Production Plant – PEP Group – South Energetic Biomass, Poland ]]></title><url><![CDATA[projects-gpbepd-pelletplant_en]]></url><meta><![CDATA[pellet plant, pep]]></meta><metad><![CDATA[]]></metad><menuOrder><![CDATA[0]]></menuOrder><menuStatus><![CDATA[]]></menuStatus><template><![CDATA[template.php]]></template><content><![CDATA[&lt;h3&gt;Introduction of &lt;small&gt;Polish Energy Partners S.A.&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another worth mentioning success of DORAN owner, Mr Andrzej Rogulski, is successful realization of project related to construction of three pellet production factories for Polish Energy Partners S.A.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These tasks were performed as a part of Andrzej Rogulski’s function as the Director of biomass fuels production in PEP Group. Currently there are three objects producing agro pellet as organic fuels that function for Polish Energy Group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Plant in Sepolno Krajenskie – PEP Group operator – North Energetic Biomass Ltd.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Plant in Zabkowice Slaskie – PEP Group operator – South Energetic Biomass Ltd.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Plant in Zamosc – PEP Group operator – East Energetic Biomass Ltd.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It should also be noted that thanks to three efficiently working plants, that total capacity is approximately 150 000&amp;nbsp; tones per year, PEP is one of the leaders in straw pellet production in Poland. Moreover, thanks to great quality of produced fuel, it supports long-term contracts with power plants and large power plants.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Description of the project &lt;small&gt;PEP Group - South Energetic Biomass &lt;/small&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At this site we present the project related with constructing the biomass processing plant in Zabkowice Slaskie which operator is PEP Group - East Energetic Biomass Ltd. Annual capacity of the plant is approximately 60,000 Mg.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Realization of the project was divided into two stages. In the first stage the first yanking and shredding line was started along with the complete section of granulation and shipping the product. Starting the first technological line and obtaining the expected capacity took place in early October 2010.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Realization of the second stage of the project, installing the second yanking and shredding line along with additional air filtration, lasted from March to May 2011.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From May 2011 biomass processing plant in Zabkowice Slaskie leads the proper production of straw pellet of 4,500 Mg monthly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As part of duties on behalf of the Polish Energy Partners Group, Director A. Rogulski was responsible for:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;the supervision and coordination of work on the design of the label,&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;perform a comprehensive supervision over the construction work,&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;perform a comprehensive supervision of assembly lines,&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;commissioning of technological start-up,&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;training of employees,&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;optimization of the production process and achieving the expected capacity of the establishment,&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;supervision of the current exlpoitation of the object.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please find below photos taken during the construction and assembly work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Gallery &lt;small&gt;PEP Group - South Energetic Biomass&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;well&quot;&gt;(% gallery name=gpbepd-pelletplant %)&lt;/div&gt;
]]></content><author><![CDATA[doran]]></author><parent><![CDATA[]]></parent><private><![CDATA[]]></private><menu><![CDATA[]]></menu><creDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 11:03:55 +0100</creDate><user><![CDATA[doran]]></user></item>
