<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<item><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 11:56:22 +0100</pubDate><title><![CDATA[Miscanthus Mother Plantation - KSG Agro Group, Ukraine]]></title><url><![CDATA[projects-ksg-miskant_en]]></url><meta><![CDATA[]]></meta><metad><![CDATA[]]></metad><menuOrder><![CDATA[0]]></menuOrder><menuStatus><![CDATA[]]></menuStatus><template><![CDATA[template.php]]></template><content><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;Another project successfully completed in May 2013 was the establishment of the Miscanthus mother plantation in Ukraine. The task was carried out under the contract with Ukrainian company KSG Agro S.A. listed at Warsaw Stock Exchange. The investment was aimed on establishing several dozen hectares Miscanthus mother plantation on the land that belongs to KSG Agro Group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the context of the conract with the Ukrainian counterpart DORAN pledged to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;proper preparation and protection of Miscanthus seedlings (rhizomes),&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;fulfill the direct supervision of planting in the regions of Dnipropetrovsk in the Ukraine,&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;conducting of regular consultations on the soil preparation before planting crops as well as subsequent exploitation of the soil.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite very little difficulties in the realization of the contract ( related with the customs in the Ukraine) the adroitness of the plantation, confirmed in autumn 2013, was estimated at a high level of 70-80%.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More information about the project can be found on the specially created website about Miscanthus: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.miskantolbrzymi.com.pl&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;http://www.miskantolbrzymi.com.pl&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The photographic documentation is attached below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Gallery &lt;small&gt;KSG Agro Group &lt;/small&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;well&quot;&gt;(% gallery name=ksg-miskant %)&lt;/div&gt;
]]></content><author><![CDATA[doran]]></author><parent><![CDATA[]]></parent><private><![CDATA[]]></private><menu><![CDATA[]]></menu><creDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 10:49:30 +0100</creDate><user><![CDATA[doran]]></user></item>
